[
    {
        "topic": "Movie question",
        "question": "What is the name of the wizarding school in the 'Harry Potter' series?",
        "possibleAnswers": ["Hogwarts", "Narnia", "Gondor", "Gotham"],
        "correctAnswer": "Hogwarts"
    },
    {
        "topic": "Movie question",
        "question": "Which animated movie features a talking lion named Simba?",
        "possibleAnswers": ["Finding Nemo", "The Lion King", "Shrek", "Toy Story 2"],
        "correctAnswer": "The Lion King"
    },
    {
        "topic": "Movie question",
        "question": "Who directed the film 'Titanic'?",
        "possibleAnswers": ["Steven Spielberg", "James Cameron", "Martin Scorsese", "Christopher Nolan"],
        "correctAnswer": "James Cameron"
    },
    {
        "topic": "Movie question",
        "question": "In which movie does a young girl follow a yellow brick road?",
        "possibleAnswers": ["Alice in Wonderland", "The Wizard of Oz", "Mary Poppins", "Harry Potter"],
        "correctAnswer": "The Wizard of Oz"
    },
    {
        "topic": "Movie question",
        "question": "What is the name of the superhero in the 'Spider-Man' movies?",
        "possibleAnswers": ["Bruce Wayne", "Peter Parker", "Clark Kent", "Tony Stark"],
        "correctAnswer": "Peter Parker"
    },
    {
        "topic": "Movie question",
        "question": "Which movie features the quote, 'I'll be back'?",
        "possibleAnswers": ["Die Hard", "Terminator", "Rambo", "Back to the Future"],
        "correctAnswer": "Terminator"
    },
    {
        "topic": "Movie question",
        "question": "In the 'Toy Story' series, what is the name of the cowboy toy?",
        "possibleAnswers": ["Buzz Lightyear", "Woody", "Rex", "Mr Potatohead"],
        "correctAnswer": "Woody"
    },
    {
        "topic": "Movie question",
        "question": "Which Disney princess has a raccoon as a sidekick?",
        "possibleAnswers": ["Ariel", "Pocahontas", "Cinderella", "Snow White"],
        "correctAnswer": "Pocahontas"
    },
    {
        "topic": "Movie question",
        "question": "What color is the infamous dress worn by the character Jessica Rabbit in 'Who Framed Roger Rabbit'?",
        "possibleAnswers": ["Red", "Blue", "Green","Yellow" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Red"
    },
    {
        "topic": "Movie question",
        "question": "In 'Finding Nemo,' what type of fish is Nemo?",
        "possibleAnswers": ["Clownfish", "Goldfish", "Betta fish", "Salmon"],
        "correctAnswer": "Clownfish"
    },
    {
        "topic": "Movie question",
        "question": "What is the name of the fictional African country in 'Black Panther'?",
        "possibleAnswers": ["Zamunda", "Wakanda", "Elbonia", "Wakandie"],
        "correctAnswer": "Wakanda"
    },
    {
        "topic": "Movie question",
        "question": "Who is the lead actor in the movie 'Pirates of the Caribbean'?",
        "possibleAnswers": ["Orlando Bloom", "Johnny Depp", "Hugh Jackman", "Leonardo di Caprio"],
        "correctAnswer": "Johnny Depp"
    },
    {
        "topic": "Movie question",
        "question": "In 'Frozen,' what magical ability does Elsa have?",
        "possibleAnswers": ["Fire manipulation", "Time travel", "Ice powers", "Invisibility"],
        "correctAnswer": "Ice powers"
    },
    {
        "topic": "Movie question",
        "question": "Which film features a dinosaur theme park?",
        "possibleAnswers": ["Jurassic Park", "King Kong", "The Land Before Time","Godzilla"],
        "correctAnswer": "Jurassic Park"
    },
    {
        "topic": "Movie question",
        "question": "What is the name of the bear in 'The Jungle Book'?",
        "possibleAnswers": ["Baloo", "Bagheera", "Shere Khan", "Mowgli"],
        "correctAnswer": "Baloo"
    },
    {
        "topic": "Movie question",
        "question": "In 'The Incredibles,' what is Mr. Incredibleâ€™s real name?",
        "possibleAnswers": ["Bob Parr", "Jack-Jack", "Dash", "Bruce Banner"],
        "correctAnswer": "Bob Parr"
    },
    {
        "topic": "Movie question",
        "question": "What song does Elsa sing in 'Frozen' when she embraces her powers?",
        "possibleAnswers": ["Let It Go", "Do You Want to Build a Snowman?", "For the First Time in Forever", "I got a friend in me"],
        "correctAnswer": "Let It Go"
    }

]